how's it going teams will be 5/5
with a very special video today and
guess what day it is
that's right it's Monday and you
know what I do on Monday ie a Sonic
Underground themed meal that's right
today I would I just I decided
to film myself eating a great delicious
our kind of meal a healthy one too so I
think we'll we will skip right to the to
the awesome power up so on Mondays I
like to watch hang on dr. Bach avenge
great DVD I recommend you buy
that right now if you don't don't own it
stop this bill right now you don't want
to be sports I'm gonna be watching an
episode while I eat my sock iron meal so
boom get this put in boom
all right and now we wait
come on any day now okay
so a pillock peel
feels like being an ass right now so
doesn't really matter I guess I mean I
have all the episodes down on my
computer anyway not not illegally Gala I
bought all of them so do not worry we
were go ahead start with one of my
favorite episode one
there we go turn that down sup
doesn't interrupt my voice I mean y'all
got to hear me anyway so time to
style so as you all remember at least if
you watched my lovey you would know that
I have song on theme foods and here they
are first of all for Bobby I get get
banana a plump fat juicy the yellowest
banana I can find
and of course for Barbies love Sonic I
get a blue Cup and inside is some heat
up blueberry tea I don't know if you can
tell if it's blue or not but trust me
it's there now for Manic I get a big
heaping ball I get salad make
sure it's bring the greenest lettuce I
could find done not any of that
bad there for Mindy I got on both
Knuckles I got red sprinkles as mostly
memento for my last video so as you can
see I have a rhythm going on Bobby is a
banana
Mindy isn't orange Sonic is always a
blue liquid Knuckles the red sprinkles
everyone else I guess I just mix and
match and oh oh no last I mean he
was a burrito I think yeah okay then
oh and of course last but not
least for dessert I got some Sonia
doughnuts they're not really that pink
but sweetie you see the end I think I'm
ready to dig in
hope you enjoy the meal
oh yeah hmm oh that's the good
Oh
hmm
oh that's a good
Oh beautiful episode suck doctor
father comes in
mmm that's good
as good bitches just rather good does to
me
I think I'm done I am sorry is
it's time I think it's time for dessert
when you say
so as I was saying for Sonia I got I got
a strawberry donut and you may be
wondering
timbi one through five but this isn't
pink well what do you say to this look
at that look at that is
chop my dawn up in this
hope you guys have fun
hope you guys had fun so I'm gonna go
ahead face watch episode soccer and
leave that in the comments what you guys
locked me on Monday